<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advice with Replacement</title>
    <link>https://gradschooladvice.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Advice with Replacement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 16:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gradschooladvice.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Surviving Grad School in the Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://gradschooladvice.github.io/posts/2020-09-28-grad-school-in-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradschooladvice.github.io/posts/2020-09-28-grad-school-in-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>A lot of this advice is generalizable to graduate school advice, even outside the context of trying to do a Ph.D. in the middle of a pandemic. I’ve found that things that used to be helpful in (1) maintaining my mental health, and (2) being able to be productive have now become crucial to hitting a baseline level of sanity and getting literally anything done.
There are a couple caveats that should be highlighted: (1) I have been lucky in the sense that my Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://gradschooladvice.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradschooladvice.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A lot of information in graduate school is shared through informal channels, like coffee chats, happy hours, and random office encounters. The goal of this blog is to try and provide a compilation of advice in a more formal setting so that everyone can have easier access to it.
Who are we? We are three PhD students who met during our remote summer internship during the summer of 2020. Specifically, our graduate programs are all somehow related to Statistics, which means that most of our posts and our knowledge generally is most applicable to people who are also in some form of a Statistics Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
